<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elston D&#39;Souza, Digital Consultant and Honours Graduate in Biomedical Science on Elston Neil D&#39;Souza</title>
    <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elston D&#39;Souza, Digital Consultant and Honours Graduate in Biomedical Science on Elston Neil D&#39;Souza</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:47:38 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://elstondsouza.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating automated literature searches within Slack : A primer to Bash tools, APIs and Webhooks</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/slackriture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:45:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/slackriture/</guid>
      <description>Keeping up-to-date with literature in research is really important. Since research is by its nature bleeding edge, being informed and constantly innundated at the very frontier is necessary for any budding researcher.
However, what are the kinds of solutions that are there for our needs? Well there is Google Scholar. But it sends updates on your specific search queries to your emails. Where it can get lost within updates.
I, for one, had unique requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the structural distribution of SARS-CoV2 mutations using COVID3D</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/covid3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:45:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/covid3d/</guid>
      <description>The COVID-19 Pandemic is still a large part of our lives. At least, here, in Melbourne (and Victoria) at large, where Stage 4 Restrictions still being enforced. All of us have been waiting for that solace from the various drugs and vaccines that have been heralded in the news.
Just recently the AstraZeneca vaccine, one of the forefront and most promising efforts, has been put on hold after a reported case of an adverse reaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reigniting your Digital Marketing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/reigniting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:45:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/reigniting/</guid>
      <description>Most small businesses around this time have started opening up again and have been looking into the different opportunities to gain their audiences back. Does marketing make sense right now? When is the right time to resume advertising and how do you go about it?
What does history tell us? Many companies that have looked past that have disregarded advertising during recessions and epidemics have been thrust to the wayside. If history has taught us anything - those who remain proactive during a crisis are often the ones who come out on top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to take your small business digital during coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:45:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/digital/</guid>
      <description>We are amidst challenging times where social distancing has stunted many business&#39; growth. While in other times, the digital space was primarily used to complement a physical presence as a lead generation mechanism, the current situation has afforded a new opportunity to enter the digital space. The beauty of digital is in the fact that virtual interactions with your customer may completely replace existing physical interactions.
Despite the allure of a setting up shop completely virtual, there are so many ways to get it wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 02:49:51 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am Elston, a student in the Department of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology at the University of Melbourne and at the Baker Heart and Diabetes Institute. I currently completed my Bachelor of Biomedicine (Degree with Honours) under the supervision of A/Prof David Ascher. My current research involves exploring the differences in mutational tolerances between different ethnic populations using large whole genome datasets and bioinformatics tools developed by the Ascher lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 02:49:51 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email : elstonndsouza@gmail.com
Phone : (+61) 422 896 554
LinkedIn : @elstonndsouza
Twitter : @elston_neil</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 02:49:51 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/publications/</guid>
      <description> Portelli, Stephanie, Moshe Olshansky, Carlos Henrique Miranda Rodrigues, Elston N. D&amp;rsquo;Souza, YooChan Myung, Michael Silk, Azadeh Alavi, Douglas EV Pires, and David B. Ascher. &amp;ldquo;Exploring the structural distribution of genetic variation in SARS-CoV-2 with the COVID-3D online resource&amp;rdquo; Nature Genetics (2020) (Joint First Author).  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
