<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elston D&#39;Souza, Digital Consultant and Honours Student in Biomedical Science  on Elston Neil D&#39;Souza</title>
    <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elston D&#39;Souza, Digital Consultant and Honours Student in Biomedical Science  on Elston Neil D&#39;Souza</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:47:38 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elstondsouza.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to take your small business digital during coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/posts/digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:45:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/posts/digital/</guid>
      <description>We are amidst challenging times where social distancing has stunted many business&amp;rsquo; growth. While in other times, the digital space was primarily used to complement a physical presence as a lead generation mechanism, the current situation has afforded a new opportunity to enter the digital space. The beauty of digital is in the fact that virtual interactions with your customer may completely replace existing physical interactions.
Despite the allure of a setting up shop completely virtual, there are so many ways to get it wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 02:49:51 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am Elston, a student in the Department of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology at the University of Melbourne and at the Baker Heart and Diabetes Institute. I am currently pursuing a Bachelor of Biomedicine (Degree with Honours) under the supervision of A/Prof David Ascher. My current research involves exploring the differences in mutational tolerances between different ethnic populations using large whole genome datasets and bioinformatics tools developed by the Ascher lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 02:49:51 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can get in touch with me in many ways: Email : elstonndsouza@gmail.com
Phone : (+61) 422 896 554
Twitter : @elston_neil
GitHub : elston-n-dsouza
LinkedIn : @elstonndsouza
Instagram : elstonndsouza</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>