<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Elston Neil D&#39;Souza</title>
    <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Elston Neil D&#39;Souza</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:45:28 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reigniting your Digital Marketing Campaign</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/reigniting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:45:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/reigniting/</guid>
      <description>Most small businesses around this time have started opening up again and have been looking into the different opportunities to gain their audiences back. Does marketing make sense right now? When is the right time to resume advertising and how do you go about it?
What does history tell us? Many companies that have looked past that have disregarded advertising during recessions and epidemics have been thrust to the wayside. If history has taught us anything - those who remain proactive during a crisis are often the ones who come out on top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to take your small business digital during coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:45:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elstondsouza.com.au/blog/digital/</guid>
      <description>We are amidst challenging times where social distancing has stunted many business&amp;rsquo; growth. While in other times, the digital space was primarily used to complement a physical presence as a lead generation mechanism, the current situation has afforded a new opportunity to enter the digital space. The beauty of digital is in the fact that virtual interactions with your customer may completely replace existing physical interactions.
Despite the allure of a setting up shop completely virtual, there are so many ways to get it wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>